CHRISTIAN F. BRUNO

VILLA RICA, GA | 678-836-3033 | CHRISTIAN.BRUNO1995@GMAIL.COM

LINKEDIN: https://www.linkedin.com/in/christian-bruno-dev/
GitHub: https://github.com/CBrunote/ | Portfolio: https://cbruno.io/

SUMMARY

Full Stack Web developer with certification from the Georgia Tech Web Development Bootcamp including 5 years of experience with customer-facing technical application support in software. Demonstrates the ability to resolve complex technical support requests and works collaboratively to drive consistent service delivery methods. Proven ability to quickly learn new skills and proactively grow in new subject matter.

SKILLS

JavaScript, HTML, CSS, React.js, Node.js, SQL Server, MongoDB, MySQL, Tailwind CSS, Bootstrap, GraphQL, Git, Github, Salesforce, Jira, MS Office Suite, Google G-Suite

EXPERIENCE

TRAPEZE SOFTWARE, REMOTE,

Application Support Analyst

October 2021 - Present

Owner of issues for a subset of demand response PASS customers. Lead resolution tasks of issues related to application as well as consulting on database or environmental issues related to the deployment of the application.

- Facilitated major version upgrades for high profile clients to maintain their satisfaction and increase revenue opportunities to add to their service portfolio.
- Reduced Backlog for clients by 20% while receiving new perfect client satisfaction reports based on customer surveys.

UBER TECHNOLOGIES INC, Atlanta, GA,

October 2020 - October 2021

Technical Consultant October 2020 – October 2021

Served as Hardware consultant for the professional services team providing remote and onsite consultations for hardware configuration, installation, and troubleshooting.

- Lead on-site training and consulting sessions.
- Created detailed installation design documents for efficient installation of vehicle peripherals.
- Created/improved essential internal and external training documentation to ensure processes are more efficient and scalable workflow.
- Managed complex project schedule to ensure billing milestones were met or adjusted appropriately.

ROUTEMATCH SOFTWARE, Atlanta, GA,

March 2018 – October 2020

Subject Matter Expert June 2019 – October 2020

Deliver Subject Matter Expertise for hardware and peripherals including tablets, vehicle logic units, automatic vehicle annunciators, automatic passenger counters, and cellular routers. De-escalate difficult customer issues, serving as an expert in troubleshooting and fixed-route product vertical. Applied knowledge of SQL to manage backend databases, while evaluating and correcting data discrepancies.

- Created detailed Jira cases for bugs, feature requests, and showstoppers for escalation to Product Developers.
- Served as an integral team member to improve fixed route product vertical focusing on efficiency and client services, leading to decreased case backlog by 50%, while significantly enhancing customer satisfaction.
- Designed a new internal and client facing document for troubleshooting hardware issues to provide to the care team.

Customer Support Specialist August 2018 – June 2019

Provided superior customer service and industry knowledge to customers for all products. Served on the front-lines of the care team taking inbound calls and emails, created cases for documentation and working issues to resolution.

- Leveraged Salesforce, phone, email, and web-based support tools to communicate status and collaborate on solutions.
- Communicated issue status to clients in a prompt and professional manner.
- Provided training to individual customers as well as lead large group webinars.

Customer Support Coordinator March 2018 – August 2018

Recruited to identify and resolve backlog of case issues by working with the Subject Matter Expert Team to identify trends and understand common issues/needs. Followed up on old/stale cases to ensure Support Specialists could focus on new issues.

- Helped the team reduced the backlog of cases by 10% before promotion to Support Specialist
- Ensured that clients' Salesforce data was up to date and cases were appropriately documented.

PROJECTS

Lyfbro

GitHub: https://github.com/CBrunote/Lyfbro/ | Live: https://lyfbro100.herokuapp.com/

- Lyfbro is a web application aimed at helping a user track activities to monitor health progress. The app provides visual feedback on activity via an interactive calendar heatmap. Users can create accounts securely to store their activities and monitor progress. The app was built using a MySQL database integrated via the Sequelize ORM. The front-end is build with Handlbars.js and Tailwind CSS. Please note that the app is hosted on Heroku and may take a second to spin up when you visit the live link.
- Tech Stack: Tailwind CSS, MySQL, Handlebars.js, Node.js, JavaScript, HTML 5

What's For Dinner

GitHub: https://github.com/CBrunote/Whats-For-Dinner | Live: https://cbrunote.github.io/Whats-For-Dinner/

- What's For Dinner is a web application created to help you find your next meal based on search an ingredient you want to
 use and adding the ingredients to your Kroger shopping list with pricing. The app uses the MealDB API to display recipes,
 ingredients lists, and a youtube video on how to cook the meal. The Kroger API is utilized to find the price per unit of each
 ingredient that gets added to your shopping list.
- Tech Stack: MealDB API, Materialize CSS, JavaScript, HTML 5, CSS 3

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development Boot Camp Certificate: Georgia Institute of Technology, Atlanta, GA

A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Node.js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handelbars.js, ReactJS, and the MERN Stack

Bachelor of Business Administration in Marketing: *University of West Georgia*, Carrollton, Georgia, Dec 2017 *Cum Laude*Beta Gamma Sigma Member: Inducted April 2017 | Dean's List: Fall 2014, Fall 2015, Spring 2016, Fall 2016,